myflfamilies.com 2018-05-21

# Privacy Statement | Florida Department of Children and Families

Thank you for visiting the MyFlFamilies.com Web site. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit the MyFlFamilies.com Web site, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit the MyFlFamilies.com portal, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved, and your personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.

If you have other questions about this privacy policy, or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@myflfamilies.com](mailto:webmaster@myflfamilies.com)
